Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files 1919-2015 MS 3009-RG 13
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Bio Files, 1919-2015; 390.66 Linear feet (391 boxes)
  - -C-
    - Coplon, Judith, 1950-1974 (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 5)
    - Coppola, Frank, 1955-1982 (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 6)
    - Coppolino, Carl, 1966-1979 (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 7)
    - Coppolino, Carmela, 1966-1979 (Offsite-box 1555, Folder 19)
    - Corallo, Anthony, 1956-1987 (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 8)
    - Cord, Errett Lobban, 1932-1974 (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 9)
    - Corelli, Franco, 1965-1973 (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 10)
    - Cori, Gerty Theresa, 1943-1984 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 1)
    - Corigliano, John, Jr., 1961-1991 (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 11)
    - Corll, Dean Arnold, 1973 (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 12)
    - Corman, Avery, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 1555, Folder 20)
    - Cormier, Lucia M. (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 13)
    - Corona, Juan V., 1971-1993 (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 15)
    - Corot, Jean Baptiste Camille, 1930-1986 (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 16-17)
    - Corrigan, Douglas Goerge, 1933-1988 (Offsite-box 1112, Folder 18)
    - Corrigan, Mairead, 1976-1988 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 1)
    - Cortes, Hernando, 1955-1987 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 2)
    - Costa Gomes, Francisco, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 3)
    - Costes, Dieudonne, 1929-1984 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 2)
    - Couch, Virgil, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 4)
    - Coughlin, Charles E., 1932-1988 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 5)
    - Courbet, Gustave, 1933-1988 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 6-7)
    - Couve De Murville, Maurice, 1945-1988 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 8-10)
    - Couzens, James, 1930-1955 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 11)
    - Cowdray, Third Viscount, 1950-1983 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 3)
    - Cowell, Henry, 1953-1965 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 12)
    - Cowles, John, 1961-1983 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 13)
    - Cowley, Malcolm, 1964-1989 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 14)
    - Cox, Archibald, 1962-1990 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 15)
    - Cox, Edward Finch, 1971-1978 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 16)
    - Cox, James M., Jr., 1930-1974 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 4)
    - Cox, Richard Dolvin, 1950-1969 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 17)
    - Cox, William S., 1952 (Offsite-box 1113, Folder 18)
    - Crabb, Lionel Kenneth, 1956-1974 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 1)
    - Craig, Edward Arthur, 1950 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 2)
    - Craig, George North, 1949-1962 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 3)
    - Craig, Mae, 1939-1964 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 5)
    - Craig, Malin, 1932-1945 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 4)
    - Craig, Marjorie, 1968-1978 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 5)
    - Cramer, Kenneth F., 1949-1954 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 6)
    - Cramer, William C., 1954-1964 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 7)
    - Crampton, James E., 1970 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 8)
    - Cranach, Lucas the Elder, 1938-1992 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 9)
    - Cranach, Lucas the Younger, 1938-1992 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 9)
    - Crane, Charles Richard, 1925-1987 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 11)
    - Crane, Hart, 1962-1986 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 12)
    - Crane, Philip M., 1963-1983 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 6)
    - Crane, Roy, 1951-1977 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 13)
    - Crane, Stephen, 1951-1986 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 14)
    - Cranston, Alan, 1961-1991 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 15)
    - Crary, Albert P., 1959-1987 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 7)
    - Crater, Joseph Force, 1930-1990 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 16)
    - Crawford, Bruce E., 1970-1989 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 8)
    - Crazy Horse, 1949-1988 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 17)
    - Credi, Lorenzo di, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 18)
    - Crespin, Regine, 1938-1989 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 19)
    - Crews, Harry, 1968-1992 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 20)
    - Crick, Francis, 1972-1993 (Offsite-box 1114, Folder 21)
    - Crimmins, Alice, 1966-1987 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 1)
    - Crimmins, Alice, 1965-1968 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 9)
    - Cripps, Stafford, 1937-1965 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 2-3)
    - Croce, Benedetto, 1934-1960 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 4)
    - Cross, James Richard, 1970-1978 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 6)
    - Crossfield, Scott, 1953-1987 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 7)
    - Crowe, William J., Jr., 1985-1992 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 8)
    - Crowther of Headingley, Baron, 1943-1972 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 9)
    - Crumb, George, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 10)
    - Crump, Edward Hull, 1939-1985 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 11)
    - Crump, Paul, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 12)
    - Cruzan, Nancy, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 13)
    - Cudlipp, Hugh, 1938-1973 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 14)
    - Cullman, Joseph F., III, 1965-1978 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 15)
    - Cummings, Homer Stille, 1933-1962 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 16)
    - Cunliffe, Marcus, 1958-1990 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 17)
    - Cunningham of Hyndhope, 1941-1982 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 18)
    - Cunningham, Harry B., 1959-1992 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 19)
    - Cunningham, John Philip, 1955-1992 (Offsite-box 1115, Folder 20)
    - Cunningham, R. Walter, 1967-1987 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 1)
    - Cunningham-Reid, Alexander, 1938-1943 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 2)
    - Cuomo, Andrew, 1982-1991 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 3)
    - Cuomo, Mario M., 1974-1993 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 4-6)
    - Curcio, Renato, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 7)
    - Curb, Mike, 1969-1981 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 8)
    - Curie, Eve, 1939-1963 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 10-11)
    - Curie, Marie, 1930-1983 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 12)
    - Curie, Pierre and Marie, 1929-1987 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 13)
    - Curley, James Michael, 1935-1993 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 9-10)
    - Currie, Lauchlin E., 1939-1965 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 11)
    - Currier and Ives, 1941-1979 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 12)
    - Currier, Stephen R., 1963-1968 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 13)
    - Curry, Jesse, 1963-1980 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 14)
    - Curry, John F., 1931-1934 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 15)
    - Curtice, Harlow Herbert, 1947-1965 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 16-18)
    - Curtin, John, 1945-1986 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 19)
    - Curtis, Charles, 1934-1989 (Offsite-box 1116, Folder 20)
    - Curtis, Charlotte, 1964-1987 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 1)
    - Curtis, Cyrus, 1932-1969 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 2)
    - Curtis, Edward Sheriff, 1972-1992 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 3)
    - Curtis, Thomas B., 1961-1972 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 4)
    - Curtiss, Glenn Hammond, 1933-1961 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 5)
    - Curzon, George Nathaniel, 1934-1984 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 6)
    - Cushing, Richard, 1944-1984 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 7-10)
    - Cushing, William B., 1936-1951 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 11)
    - Custer, George Armstrong, 1932-1992 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 12-14)
    - Cutler, Robert, 1946-1974 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 15)
    - Cutten, Arthur William, 1931-1967 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 16)
    - Cvetic, Matthew, 1956-1962 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 17)
    - Cynthia, 1963 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 18)
    - Cyrano de Bergerac (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 19)
    - Cyril, Grand Duke of Russia, 1924-1938 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 20)
    - Cyril, Saint, 1963-1985 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 21)
  - -D-
    - Dacey, Norman F., 1967-1992 (Offsite-box 1117, Folder 22)
    - Dabney, Virginius, 1943-1956 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 1)
    - Dahrendorf, Ralf, 1973-1975 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 2)
    - Daimler, Gottlieb, 1957-1981 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 3)
    - Dale, Henry Hallett, 1936-1968 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 4)
    - Daley, Richard J., 1953-1993 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 5-11)
    - Daley, Robert, 1961-1985 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 12)
    - Dali, Salvador, 1936-1979 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 13)
    - Dalitz, Moe B., 1963-1989 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 14)
    - Dallek, Robert, 1982-1992 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 15)
    - Daly sisters, 1949-1966 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 16)
    - Daly, Dan, 1937-1960 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 17)
    - Damaskinos, Archbishop, 1944-1949 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 18)
    - Damrosch, Walter, 1929-1975 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 19)
    - Damien, Father, 1932-1980 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 20)
    - Dana, Charles Anderson, 1959-1982 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 21)
    - Dandolos, Nick, 1931-1967 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 22)
    - Danforth, Douglas D., 1978-1990 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 23)
    - Danforth, John C., 1974-1990 (Offsite-box 1118, Folder 24)
    - Daniel, Clifton, Jr., 1955-1987 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 1)
    - Daniel, Price, 1957-1967 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 2)
    - Daniel, Yuli M., 1965-1988 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 3)
    - Danielou, Jean, 1966-1982 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 4)
    - Daniels, Jonathan Myrick (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 5)
    - Daniels, Josephus, 1938-1976 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 6)
    - D'Annunzio, Gabriele, 1928-1984 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 7)
    - Dante, 1933-1985 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 8-11)
    - Daoud, Abu, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 12)
    - D'Aquino, Iva Toguri, 1949-1975 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 13)
    - Dare, Virginia, 1939-1987 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 14)
    - Darlan, Jean Francois, 1939-1966 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 15)
    - Darling, Frank, 1932-1963 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 16)
    - Darman, Richard G., 1984-1990 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 17)
    - Da Rocha, Francisco Brochado, 1962-1987 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 18)
    - Darrow, Gerard, 1941-1982 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 19)
    - Darst, David, 1968-1989 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 20)
    - Dart, Raymond A., 1939-1988 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 21)
    - Darwin, Charles Galton, 1938-1989 (Offsite-box 1119, Folder 22)
    - Darwin, Charles Robert, 1937-1992 (Offsite-box 1119)
    - Darwin, Charles Robert, 1937-1992 (Offsite-box 1160)
    - Das, Kamala, 1976 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 4)
    - Dash, Samuel, 1973-1977 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 5)
    - D'Aubuisson, Roberto, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 6)
    - Daugherty, Harry Micajah, 1941-1981 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 7)
    - Daughtry, Herbert D., 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 8)
    - Daumier, Honore, 1930-1992 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 9-10)
    - Davenport, Guy, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 11)
    - David, 1972-1984 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 12)
    - David, Jacques Louis, 1952-1992 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 13)
    - Davidson, Frank P., 1961-1984 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 14)
    - Davidson, Sara, 1969-1989 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 15)
    - Davies, John Paton, Jr., 1945-1969 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 16)
    - Davies, Joseph Edward, 1937-1982 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 17-18)
    - Davies, Peter Maxwell, 1971-1989 (Offsite-box 1160, Folder 19)
    - Davies, Robertson, 1975-1991 (Offsite-box 1161, Folder 1)
    - Davignon, Etienne, 1974-1984 (Offsite-box 1161, Folder 2)
    - Da Vinci, Leonardo, 1965-1992 (Offsite-box 1161, Folder 3-10)
    - Davis, Adelle, 1962-1984 (Offsite-box 1161, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Anthony, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 1161, Folder 12)
    - Davis, Benjamin Oliver, Jr., 1954-1965 (Offsite-box 1161, Folder 13)
    - Davis, Colin, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 1161, Folder 14)
    - Davis, Edgar B., 1929-1942 (Offsite-box 1161, Folder 15)
    - Davis, Elmer, 1942-1977 (Offsite-box 1161, Folder 16)
    - Davis, Evelyn Y., 1982-1991 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 1)
    - Davis, J. Mason, 1968-1974 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 2)
    - Davis, James Houston, 1947-1961 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 3)
    - Davis, Jefferson, 1927-1991 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 4-5)
    - Davis, John William, 1932-1985 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 6)
    - Davis, Loyal Edward, 1962-1985 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 7)
    - Davis, Norman Hezekiah, 1932-1944 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 8)
    - Davis, Patricia White, 1965-1983 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 9)
    - Davis, Rennie C., 1969-1984 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 10)
    - Davis, Richard Harding, 1933-1961 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Stuart, 1944-1991 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 12-13)
    - Davis, T. Cullen, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 14)
    - Davis, Thomas J., 1962-1985 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 15)
    - Davis, William Grenville, 1970-1985 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 16)
    - Davison, Frederick Trubee, 1925-1951 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 17)
    - Dawkins, Peter M., 1958-1991 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 18)
    - Dawson, Charles, 1938-1980 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 19)
    - Dawson, Christopher, 1935-1960 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 20)
    - Dawson, William L., 1945-1986 (Offsite-box 1162, Folder 21)
    - Dayan, Moshe, 1948-1990 (Offsite-box 1162)
    - Dayan, Moshe, 1948-1990 (Offsite-box 1163)
    - Dayan, Ruth, 1956-1985 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 3)
    - Dayan, Yael, 1959-1985 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 4)
    - Days, Drew Saunders, III, 1966-1992 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 5)
    - Day-Lewis, Cecil, 1938-1977 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 6)
    - Deak, Nicholas, 1963-1985 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 7)
    - Dealey, George Bannerman, 1937-1986 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 8)
    - Dean, Gordon Evans, 1951-1979 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 9)
    - Dean, John Wesley, III, 1969-1992 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 10-12)
    - Dean, Maureen, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 13)
    - Dean, Morton, 1960-1986 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 14)
    - Dean, William Frishe, 1938-1981 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 15)
    - Deardourff, John D., 1964-1992 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 16)
    - Deacer, Michael K., 1980-1992 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 17)
    - De Azevedo, Jose Batista Pineiro, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 18)
    - De Bakey, Michael E., 1953-1980 (Offsite-box 1163, Folder 19-20)
    - De Beistegui, Carlos, 1951-1970 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 1)
    - De Boer, Jessica, 1993 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 2)
    - De Borchgrave, Arnaud, 1969-1975 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 4)
    - De Bono, Edward, 1964-1991 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 3)
    - DeBray, Regis, 1967-1975 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 5)
    - Debre, Michel, 1958-1980 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 6)
    - Debs, Eugene Victor, 1940-1985 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 7)
    - Debus, Kurt H., 1959-1983 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 8)
    - Debussy, Claude, 1925-1985 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 9-11)
    - De Carlo, Angelo, 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 12)
    - De Carlo, Charles R., 1966-1983 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 13)
    - De Carvalho, Otelo Saraiva, 1973-1989 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 14)
    - De Castries, Christian, 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 15)
    - De Cavalcante, Simone Rizzo, 1967-1971 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 16)
    - De Chirico, Giorgio, 1951-1989 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 17-18)
    - Decio, Arthur Julius, 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 19)
    - De Courcy, Kenneth, 1950-1963 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 20)
    - De Crow, Karen, 1974-1980 (Offsite-box 1164, Folder 21)
    - Dector, Midge, 1967-1989 (Offsite-box 1165, Folder 1)
    - Dederich, Charles E., 1961-1980 (Offsite-box 1165, Folder 2)
    - De Dios, Manuel, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 1165, Folder 3)
    - De Falla, Maneul, 1945-1966 (Offsite-box 1165, Folder 4)
    - Defoe, Daniel, 1960-1989 (Offsite-box 1165, Folder 5)
    - De Franco, Gabriel, 1966-1969 (Offsite-box 1165, Folder 6)
    - De Funis, Marco, Jr., 1974 (Offsite-box 1165, Folder 7)
    - De Gaitani, Jan, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 1165, Folder 8)
    - De Galardo-Terraube, Genevieve, 1956-1973 (Offsite-box 1165, Folder 9)
    - De Galinez, Jesus, 1956-1964 (Offsite-box 1165, Folder 10-13)
    - Degas, Edgar, 1932-1988 (Offsite-box 1165)
    - Degas, Edgar, 1932-1988 (Offsite-box 1166)
    - De Gasperi, Alcide, 1944-1954 (Offsite-box 1166, Folder 3-5)
    - De Gaulle family, 1957-1970 (Offsite-box 1166, Folder 6)
    - De Gaulle, Charles, 1945-1992 (Offsite-box 1166)
    - De Gaulle, Charles, 1945-1992 (Offsite-box 1167)
    - De Gaulle, Charles, 1945-1992 (Offsite-box 1168)
    - DeGraff, Robert Fair, 1939-1990 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 14)
    - De Hartog, Jan, 1952-1984 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 15)
    - Dekker, Wisse, 1977-1990 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 5)
    - De Klerk, Frederick Willem, 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 6)
    - De Kooning, Willem, 1975-1993 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 7)
    - Delacroix, Eugene, 1930-1991 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 8-9)
    - De la Madrid, Miguel, 1982-1985 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 10)
    - De la Mare, Walter, 1948-1984 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 11)
    - De Larrocha, Alicia, 1967-1974 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 12)
    - De la Tour, Georges, 1936-1990 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 13)
    - De Lattre De Tassigny, Jean, 1942-1967 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 14)
    - Delaunay, Robert, 1947-1991 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 15)
    - Delaunay, Sonia, 1968-1991 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 16)
    - Delay, Dorothy, 1980-1988 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 17)
    - De Lessers, Ferdinand, 1951-1978 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 18)
    - Delgado, Jose M., 1953-1976 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 19)
    - Delia, Diane, 1982 (Offsite-box 1168, Folder 20)
    - Delibes, Leo, 1964-1981 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 1)
    - Delillo, Don, 1971-1988 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 2)
    - Della Croce, Anniello, 1966-1987 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 3)
    - Della Robbia, Andrea, 1966-1982 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 4)
    - Della Joio, Norman, 1945-1989 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 5)
    - Dellums, Ronald V., 1974-1992 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 6)
    - Del Monaco, Mario, 1950-1992 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 7)
    - Deloria, Vine V., Jr., 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 16)
    - Delors, Jacques, 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 8)
    - De Los Angeles, Victoria, 1950-1979 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 9)
    - Del Tredici, David, 1963-1991 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 10)
    - De Madariaga, Salvador, 1931-1978 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 11)
    - Demara, Ferdinand Waldo, Jr., 1951-1982 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 12)
    - De Mello, Fernando Collor, 1992 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 13)
    - De Menil, Dominique, 1963-1992 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 14)
    - Deming, W. Edwards, 1960-1990 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 15)
    - Demjanjuk, John, 1982-1991 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 16)
    - Denard, Robert, 1964-1992 (Offsite-box 1169, Folder 17)
    - Deng, Xiaoping, 1959-1989 (Offsite-box 1169)
    - Deng, Xiaoping, 1959-1989 (Offsite-box 1170)
    - Deng, Yingchao, 1946-1979 (Offsite-box 1170, Folder 7)
    - Dennis, Eugene, 1949-1961 (Offsite-box 1170, Folder 8)
    - Denson, John Lee, 1961-1982 (Offsite-box 1170, Folder 9)
    - Dengler, Dieter, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 1170, Folder 10)
    - Dent, Harry S., 1969-1992 (Offsite-box 1170, Folder 11)
    - Denton, Jeremiah A., 1980-1987 (Offsite-box 1170, Folder 12)
    - Depreist, James, 1956-1993 (Offsite-box 1170, Folder 13)
    - Derain, Andre, 1934-1992 (Offsite-box 1170, Folder 14)
    - Derian, Patricia, 1969-1992 (Offsite-box 1170, Folder 15)
    - De Sade, Marquis, 1939-1993 (Offsite-box 1170, Folder 16-17)
    - Desai, Morargi Ranchhodji, 1958-1981 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 1)
    - De Sapio, Carmine, 1940-1987 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 2-4)
    - Descartes, Rene, 1938-1986 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 5)
    - De Seversky, Alexander Prokofieff, 1938-1974 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 6)
    - Deskey, Donald, 1930-1989 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 7)
    - De Spinola, Antionio, 1974 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 8)
    - De Stael, Nicolas, 1953-1990 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 9)
    - De Tocqueville, Alexis, 1946-1988 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 10-12)
    - Deutsch, Martin, 1960-1968 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 13)
    - De Valera, Eamon, 1927-1975 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 14-15)
    - De Voto, Bernard, 1961-1975 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 16)
    - De Vries, Folkje and Tsjitske, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 17)
    - De Vries, Peter, 1959-1985 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 18)
    - De Vries, William C., 1984 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 19)
    - De Waart, Edo, 1964-1992 (Offsite-box 1171, Folder 20)
    - Dewey, John, 1929-1992 (Offsite-box 1172, Folder 1-3)
    - De Zurbaran, Francisco, 1938-1990 (Offsite-box 1172, Folder 4)
    - Diamond, David, 1959-1991 (Offsite-box 1172, Folder 6)
    - Diamond, Legs, 1930-1984 (Offsite-box 1172, Folder 7)
    - Diamond, Martin, 1966-1977 (Offsite-box 1172, Folder 8)
    - Dibelius, Otto, 1947-1967 (Offsite-box 1172, Folder 9)
    - Dicther, Misha, 1966-1992 (Offsite-box 1172, Folder 10)
    - Dickens, Charles, 1930-1993 (Offsite-box 1172)
    - Dickens, Charles, 1930-1993 (Offsite-box 1173)
    - Dickey, Herbert Spencer, 1930-1938 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 3)
    - Diderot, Denis, 1949-1991 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 4)
    - Diefenbaker, John, 1969-1984 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 5)
    - Dienstbier, Jiri, 1988-1992 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 6)
    - Dies, Martin, 1938-1961 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 7)
    - Diesel, Rudolf, 1936-1976 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 17)
    - Dietrich, Noah, 1954-1982 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 8)
    - Dietrich, Sepp, 1944-1956 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 9)
    - Diligenti quintuplets, 1944-1968 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 10)
    - Dillard, Annie, 1974-1990 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 11)
    - Dillinger, Leon, 1982 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 12)
    - Dillingham family, 1948-1963 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 13)
    - Dillon family, 1933-1991 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 14)
    - Dillon, Clarence Douglas, 1961-1987 (Offsite-box 1173, Folder 15-17)
    - Dillon, Clarence Douglas, 1953-1960 (Offsite-box 1174, Folder 1)
    - Dillon, Thomas C., 1962-1977 (Offsite-box 1174, Folder 2)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson, 1958-1988 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 18)
    - Dilworth, Richardson, 1949-1986 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 19)
    - Dimitrov, Georgi, 1934-1990 (Offsite-box 1174, Folder 3)
    - Dines, James, 1961-1991 (Offsite-box 1174, Folder 4)
    - Dinesen, Isak, 1934-1992 (Offsite-box 1174, Folder 5-7)
    - Dinkins, David N., 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 1174, Folder 8)
    - Dirks, Rudolph, 1948-1978 (Offsite-box 1174, Folder 9)
    - Dirksen, Everett McKinley, 1942-1993 (Offsite-box 1174, Folder 10-13)
    - Di Salle, Michael V., 1950-1980 (Offsite-box 1174, Folder 14-16)
    - Disraeli, Benjamin, 1931-1990 (Offsite-box 1174, Folder 17-18)
    - Divine, Father, 1943-1989 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 1)
    - Dix, Dorothy, 1939-1967 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 2)
    - Djilas, Milovan, 1959-1992 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 3)
    - Djugashvili, Yakov, 1941-1967 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 20)
    - Dobrynin, Anatoli F., 1961-1992 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 4)
    - Dobzhansky, Theodosius, 1932-1981 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 5)
    - Docking, Robert B., 1963-1983 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 21)
    - Dodd, Thomas J., 1960-1972 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 6)
    - Dodds, Harold Willis, 1934-1957 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 7)
    - Dodge family, 1930-1989 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 8)
    - Dodge, Horace E., 1936-1989 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 22)
    - Dodge, Horace Elgin, Jr., 1939-1965 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 9)
    - Doe, Baby Jane, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 10)
    - Doenitz, Karl, 1941-1985 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 11)
    - Doheny, Edward Laurence, 1927-1986 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 23)
    - Dohrn, Bernadine Rae, 1968-1993 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 12)
    - Doi, Takako, 1987-1989 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 13)
    - Dolci, Danilo, 1958-1970 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 14)
    - Dole, Elizabeth Hanford, 1971-1989 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 15)
    - Dole, Robert Joseph, 1962-1992 (Offsite-box 1175, Folder 16-18)
    - Dollfuss, Engelbert, 1934-1979 (Offsite-box 1176, Folder 1)
    - Donatello, 1932-1989 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 24)
    - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1930-1993 (Offsite-box 1176, Folder 2-3)
    - Donleavy, James Patrick, 1958-1990 (Offsite-box 1176, Folder 4)
    - Donlon, Roger Hugh C., 1964-1988 (Offsite-box 1176, Folder 5)
    - Donne, John, 1926-1987 (Offsite-box 1556, Folder 25)
    - Donovan, William Joseph, 1964-1988 (Offsite-box 1176, Folder 6)